Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching!
Best regards
Seino
Oh!
Thank you.
I'm having fun.
good luck!
I'll be painting and talking.
In the long night, completely lost in the action.
Lost in the Dromelo, far away, with a bare face
In the long night, completely lost in the action
Lost in the long night, lost in the dromero, I'll take the smile that's stolen from me
Pushing through the night, I feel like I've had a hard time, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely.
I have to hide in the murk, I have to hide in the murk, I have to expose everything that's really going on.
I got to know you better than the three of us.
I wanted to write a song that we could talk about.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
All of you.
Thank you very much.
Spring Bread Machine
It's not Spring Bread Machine.
Spring bread machine.
No, no, no.
Congratulations
Congratulations!
Did you see me with everyone?
I know it's early.
Okay, so...
Thank you all for coming to the One Ship Spring Fun Festival today.
Thank you for coming to the Spring Fan Festival.
Thank you very much.
It's like a close distance, you know, physically close.
I hope you can enjoy yourself in an at-home atmosphere.
Please take care of us until the end.
Thank you very much.
A 10,000 steps system showdown, a monomaniacal high score game, and one impromptu willow showdown for one set.
And to the winner, since today is the Spring Bread Festival, what bread!
Bread will be given away.
I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
Now then, Hirokan.
Will it be the 7th generation vs. Miko?
Manpoke showdown
Yo, let's go!
Yes, let's start!
Go for it! Go, go, go!
Oh, great! Stop crushing each other!
Please stop it!
My score is 111!
Oh, wow! That's great!
My hands are shaking. It's going up by one now.
Are you at 114?
Shall I make it 114?
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Boom!
Don!
Huh!
One hundred!
2!
It's 2!
Nagase wins!
Congratulations!
This is Misato Matsuda.
The winner is the one who wins the most times out of three.
Luka looks embarrassed. Lilika looks like she's not very good.
I'll go with Lilika.
Let's see who gets the highest score in the mimicry contest.
Let's start with Lilika.
Me? Anpanman!
That's not me.
I'm Anpanman.
Oh, isn't this good?
Well, here's Milica's Anpanman.
Bunk!
Anpanman!
So, who looked more like Anpanman?
Good match?
I would like to answer.
Who thinks Millimeter was better?
You won this one.
You won this one?
Who thinks Milica was better?
About the same?
Not at all.
Have you seen Anpanman?
Yes, I have.
I've already decided on this one.
Oh, you have?
You already knew the theme.
Did you?
Can I decide?
Yes, yes.
I didn't know.
Well...
We were talking about it backstage.
That's a serious question.
I don't like it when people do that.
That's okay, I won't use the funniest part.
Yeah, it makes a difference who comes.
I mean, you can't see it, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll be back in June with the Lance prize.
I've seen some of the things that you've seen, and I'm hoping to do a lot more.
I'm hoping to do a lot of enrichment.
I hope you'll continue to be with us at Ursip.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Well then, I'll see you again.
Yes, ma'am.
Come here.
I'll see you soon.
Thank you very much for coming today.
That's all for us, the standard of D-Live.
BURSTAR.
Thank you very much.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
One Ship Spring Fan Festival
So, hello everyone.
Good afternoon.
It's the second part of the Wanship Spring Fan Festival.
Thank you all for coming.
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're going to have a game of fetch.
You write a theme in a relay style.
And then we will try to answer the question at the end of the game. If the members are connected to the end of the game, it is a success.
No group games, no long-distance competitions, no fights.
No fighting, no long-distance competitions, and no fights.
Well then, here are the subjects.
Go, go, go, go!
Dong, dong, dong...
What? Huh? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Huh? He's saying, "Huh?
Is it okay?
Now let's see Luke's drawing.
Oh, I see. You're not allowed to look.
I'm not allowed to look?
What? Can't I look at it too?
Did you see it?
What an idiot.
You didn't see it? Did you see it?
Yes, I did.
Did you?
Oh, wow.
That good?
That's great. I'm amazing. That's great.
I can only see this way.
Here I go.
Ready, go!
Oh, wow.
You know what I mean?
It's good, right?
I know.
Just because Ririka understands this,
I don't think it's safe to say that you know what's going on, right?
Yes, I did.
I wrote it.
Okay, let me see it.
Here it is.
D'oh.
You're doing really well, aren't you?
I'm really good with notes.
Anyone can do it.
Clean this up.
This is also supposed to be cleaning.
I see.
I drew this.
What? It doesn't look like what you were doing before?
It's fine.
Let's see...
The big guy from work.
They're invited to a dinner party, and all the guys are there,
Listening to poop songs.
I thought.
What?
Drunk.
Boss? Human?
One of these is a panda.
Ha!
Ah!
Oh, this one.
This one.
Can I try to put it together nicely?
It's hard! Panda Boss's...
I'm Boss Panda's
A bad recital?
That's what I wanted to say.
But listen to me.
It's beer.
Beer. Where does beer come from?
It looks like beer to me.
There's no beer.
No, it's not beer.
Your eyes are all puffy.
That's what I always say.
In my opinion.
I don't think that's the way you want to hear it.
A bear playing live.
Correct.
Well, look...
You were in the show with the comedian, right?
Isn't that right? Mika, I'm...
Here, look.
Yum!
This, this, this.
No, no, no.
This is this one!
It's been a while since we've had a fan club event.
And we're really just doing this kind of talk?
Almost.
We haven't done anything like this in a while, so it was kind of fresh,
Thank you very much again to everyone who came today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for coming to the Spring Can Festival.
Today's singer was our leader, Standard,
Burster.
Thank you very much.
Pappa.
The end of the show.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please take care of my dad too.
Please take care of him.
I'm sorry.
Yum.
Delicious.
Yummy.
I've never had anything like this before.
Chocolate Genesee is in it.
Delicious.
I bought a half portion of this.
I'm going to apply it to some kind of prepared miso, and I'll have it.
Oh, I see, the cash register is cute.
Once, from what this cup?
Look, one time.
Look at it a lot?
It's just a look. It's free.
This one's got a little grain in it.
Mmm.
I'm gonna eat it.
Looks good.
Mmmm...
I'm scared.
You can eat it, but it's still on the video.
Because we can all eat it.
Can I eat this? No.
Oh, my God.
I'm trying to hide it right now.
Did you eat the rest of it?
All right, then.
This is the handcrab next door.
I didn't buy it.
You're such a loser, you're gonna hurt yourself.
I creamed it.
It's delicious!
I bought it. It's delicious.
How's it taste?
Bread that betrays you.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's amazingly good.
Bread that breaks the rules might taste good.
It's delicious.
It's a bread festival.
It's a bread festival!
Thank you, Bread Festival!
Thank you very much.
From now on.
Hmmm...
What do you think?
A piece of bread to lift and eat.